{
    "subject": "resource/Shin-Keisei_Line",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shin-Keisei_Line",
    "human_readable": "The Shin-Keisei Line is primarily about Shin-Keisei Line.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9826236367225647,
            "question": "What is the Shin-Keisei Line primarily about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9473985433578491,
            "question": "What kind of line is the Shin-Keisei Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8722752928733826,
            "question": "Is the Shin-Keisei Line a type of transportation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.868334174156189,
            "question": "Are there any unique features or characteristics of the Shin-Keisei Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8272307515144348,
            "question": "What is the history of the Shin-Keisei Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8033677935600281,
            "question": "Where does the Shin-Keisei Line operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7873146533966064,
            "question": "What are the benefits of using the Shin-Keisei Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6945089101791382,
            "question": "Does the Shin-Keisei Line connect to other transportation systems?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6891177296638489,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks or destinations along the Shin-Keisei Line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6625896096229553,
            "question": "How long is the Shin-Keisei Line?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Shin-Keisei Line is primarily about Shin-Keisei Line.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4451_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable landmarks or destinations along the Shin-Keisei Line?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4451_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the Shin-Keisei Line connect to other transportation systems?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4451_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the benefits of using the Shin-Keisei Line?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4451_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4451_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as all four documents mention the Shin-Keisei Line, and the main topic of each document is indeed about the Shin-Keisei Line."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Shin-Keisei Line, including its operations and history, which supports the statement that \"The Shin-Keisei Line is primarily about Shin-Keisei Line.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}